matchmovegames.com 2012-07-24

# Privacy Policy - MatchMove Games

  1. ### INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

General

MatchMove Games collects personal information when you register with MatchMove Games, when you use MatchMove Games products or services, when you visit MatchMove Games pages or the pages of certain MatchMove Games partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. MatchMove Games may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we might also ask for your address, social security number, identification number, and information about your assets. When you register with MatchMove Games and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. MatchMove Games collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

MatchMove Games automatically receives and records information from your computer and browser, including your IP address, MatchMove Games cookie information, software and hardware attributes, and the page you request. MatchMove Games uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

  2. ### INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

MatchMove Games does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

    1. We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with MatchMove Games under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help MatchMove Games communicate with you about offers from MatchMove Games and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.
    2. We have a parent’s permission to share the information if the user is a child under age 13. Parents have the option of allowing MatchMove Games to collect and use their child’s information without consenting to MatchMove Games sharing of this information with people and companies who may use this information for their own purposes.
    3. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
    4. We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of MatchMove Games’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
    5. We transfer information about you if MatchMove Games is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, MatchMove Games will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.
    6. MatchMove Games displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.
    7. MatchMove Games does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
    8. MatchMove Games advertisers include financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies).

  3. ### COOKIES

MatchMove Games may set and access MatchMove Games cookies on your computer. MatchMove Games lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies’ use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to MatchMove Games’s cookies.

MatchMove Games uses web beacons to access MatchMove Games cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with MatchMove Games products and services.

  4. ### YOUR ABILITY TO EDIT AND DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT INFORMATION AND PREFERENCES

General

You can edit your MatchMove Games Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. New categories of marketing communications might be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the MatchMove Games service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the MatchMove Games Newsletter, that are considered part of your MatchMove Games account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect personal information about you.

  5. ### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

MatchMove Games may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your MatchMove Games account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

Questions and Suggestions

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, ZIP code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we might also ask for your address, social security number, identification number, and information about your assets. When you register with MatchMove Games and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. MatchMove Games collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of financial products and services that we offer.

If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at:

120 Lower Delta Road, #15-06 Cendex Centre, Singapore 169208

Tel: (65) 6536 7388

Email : [cs@matchmovegames.com](mailto:cs@matchmovegames.com)

There may be discrepancies in the translations from the original English versions. If there are any discrepancies between the information provided on Privacy Policy on the MatchMove Games website in English and the translation of that information in other language, the English version on the MatchMove Games website shall govern. Any such discrepancies are not binding and are of no legal effect.
